I was heading home from my trip last
week but before we did we got to stop by
Luke Sands house to visit with her for a
while and enjoy her cozy little cabin by
the sea
her family built it a long time ago and
it is full of many lovely memories
the mornings here feel like true October
the trees are magnificent all brown and
yellow and red painting the roads and
walkways with a patchwork of autumn
Magic
I simply had to spend the day wandering
and soaking in the atmosphere the air
had a crisp minty scent distinctive
chilly mornings and I decided to gamble
my luck on picking an old book from the
library to read Outdoors
[Music]
I actually got to learn a bit about the
author and found the sweet quote that I
shall paraphrase
take a moment to consider the Romantic
expedition you're on meaning that we
should all stop and remember our story
is only as Whimsical as we perceive it
and make sure to take some notes in the
process to remember your adventures
I certainly found myself using my
journal more than usual on this trip a
useful tool when immersing yourself in
the beauty of imagination
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I find that no matter where I am in a
city or out in the wilderness it is
listening to my child's heart that
guides me to imbue a bit of Whimsy into
the season whether it's a morning walk
or an evening under blankets watching my
favorite movies
I will share my tips for enjoying
October in the last part of this video
[Music]
now on our way back home we did stumble
upon a wonderful farm and pumpkin patch
and walked away with two wagon fulls of
pumpkins if you had the opportunity to
go to a pumpkin patch I highly recommend
it during the week when we went it was
so quiet and we enjoyed the entire field
to ourselves
I will leave the information about this
particular Farm down below because if
you're in the area you should stop by as
the farmer was so kind and helpful
[Music]
foreign
having loaded our Treasure of pumpkins
in our little car we headed home over
the mountains
[Music]
I had missed my pets and it was so
lovely to see them and settle back in as
they had been with my family while we
were away
there's nothing like coming home after a
getaway to be ever grateful to have the
Love of Animals loved ones and even our
houseplants waiting for us
sending my love to you this October and
let me know if you have any lovely or
spooky adventures planned this season
take care
[Music]
thank you
foreign
I am back from my trip it is so exciting
we are not gone for that long much less
than a week but it still you know gives
you time to miss home and miss your
animals and it makes it really special
coming home and saying hello to everyone
and seeing how excited everyone is it
was just it was wonderful it was
wonderful I just wanted to mention
really quick that I have reopened and
restocked my Etsy Shop finally I have so
many prints now I'm very grateful it
took me a while to find supplies to
print but my uh mushroom Bunny and some
other of my prints that have been out of
stock for a long time are now here I'm
adding some extra gifts to each and
every order in the form of some stickers
and bookmarks and I will leave the
details down below as well just as a
thank you and a holiday season thank you
I also have some new prints that I've
been working on on for a while and again
I appreciate your support of this
channel so yes our car was pretty much
full of pumpkins we got so many pumpkins
that that pumpkin patch it was just so
fun so if you're ever in that area I'll
leave the details down below for you to
check it out surprisingly despite going
to a bookstore and mini antique shops
with a lot of old books I did not come
home with any new books and that was
really good do let me know what you love
to do in October and what it's like for
you I know it is definitely not cold and
autumnal depending where you live you
know I really think of course though
every month every season can be really
special even though it is not cold and
chilly where you are and it is not
Autumn I did want to share though a few
things that I do in October or perhaps
more techniques I use to really immerse
myself into things that I love and one
would be nature walks of course nature
walks are pretty selfish explanatory you
know if you have access to even a small
amount of nature like a park or
something like that it could be really
special what I would add to my nature
walk that might be helpful to you
besides of course bringing um you know
earbuds to listen to music in an
audiobook if you wish if it would help
you enjoy the experience more I find
music for me is really helpful
especially if I'm on a hike and I'm
getting a little bit tired and I want
something to keep motivating me moving a
little bit forward and challenging
myself another thing I like to do is to
bring an activity so I can sit down
somewhere nice and catch my breath for
me I really enjoy bringing a book or a
journal or something and just spending a
few minutes Outdoors really focused on
that task and I find that it's often
very enjoyable and a lot of creativity
and new ideas strike when you are
Outdoors it is rather magical and
enchanting that way another thing I do
which I have not heard too many people
do but it is really interesting is to
bring a compass with you most people
have one on their phone
um but you can also bring a physical one
as well I find it really interesting to
orient myself in the space and be aware
of kind of where I'm sitting in terms of
the terrain and the planet as a whole
another thing I'd like to do is have a
plant or animal identification app on my
phone of course they are not always
perfect but if you're just interested to
try to learn a little more about your
area it can be absolutely fascinating
the most simple most uninteresting
looking Leaf can often
send you down a rabbit hole of
information I know for me I find it
fascinating to just photograph leaves
and put them in my identification app
because the things you learn are just
incredible another thing I like to do is
often bring a book with little strips of
wax paper or a mini flower press with me
because then I can collect some fallen
leaves and all other types of little
things that I find and press them so
that they don't get ruined on the trip
back and then I can use them to create
some art and of course I think no autumn
day is the same without some evenings
spent cozied up in your blanket watching
some of your favorite movies there are
some really goofy movies that I love to
watch this time of year one of them is
the Court Jester with Danny K it's a
really old movie and I'm I'm certain
that if I watched it now I would not
necessarily ever watch it again but
because I grew up with it it just
happened to be an old DVD that my
parents had
um I have just grown to love that movie
so I always re-watch it it's extremely
silly it reminds me a lot of the cartoon
uh Disney version of Robin Hood it's
kind of got a lot of that um slapstick
comedy feel I also really love to watch
the BBC version of Sense and Sensibility
I think from 2008 I don't think it's
particularly set in Autumn but it is
very stormy and kind of foggy and Misty
a lot of the atmosphere in it and I just
think it's a wonderful
um telling of the story and I really
really enjoy it I do really also love to
watch Stardust this time of year I know
that is definitely a cult classic that
many people love I also grew up watching
the movie pagemaster which I think is
also a pretty goofy movie I have not
re-watched it but I'm planning to this
Autumn I'm gonna try going back and
re-watching a lot of those Classics that
were an important part of my childhood
so we will see how it goes so I hope
that all of you can share your
recommendations of good autumnal movies
and TV shows with all that being said I
hope that this season you can really
listen to that inner child and really
give it a little bit of love and nurture
I think we all have that little child in
our hearts that just really wants to you
know and be in the moment and really
enjoy those kind of silly little things
that we might sometimes be a little bit
self-conscious about and I think it's
really important to be aware of that
side of ourselves you know and and
embrace it thank you so much to everyone
who has purchased my book it is coming
out in November at the end of November
there's also links to Amazon and
international options down below thank
you so much for your support of my work
my writing this channel it makes all the
difference for me and I am so incredibly
grateful to all of you to give me this
opportunity I'm sending all of you my
love take care I will see you soon and
I'm gonna go play with the very playful
kitten okay goodbye
[Music]